UNESCO Second Canadian Archaeological Expedition to Carthage Records MS210
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Excavation site images, 1905 -- 2002; MS210.004; 7.45 Linear Feet; 1424 Digital Object(s)
  - ODN 2000, MS210.004.025
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00018 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00019 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00020 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00021 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00022 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00023 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00024 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00025 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00026 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00027 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00028 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00029 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00030 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00031 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00032 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00033 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00034 (Box 16)
    - ODN 2000, MS210.004.016.00035 (Box 16)
  - ODN 2001, MS210.004.026
    - ODN 2001, MS210.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
    - ODN 2001, MS210.004.017.00002 (Box 17)
    - ODN 2001, MS210.004.017.00003 (Box 17)
    - ODN 2001, MS210.004.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - ODN 2002, MS210.004.027
    - ODN 2002, MS210.004.017.00005 (Box 17)
    - ODN 2002, MS210.004.017.00006 (Box 17)
    - ODN 2002, MS210.004.017.00007 (Box 17)
    - ODN 2002, MS210.004.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Maps, 1992; MS210.004.028
    - Maps, 1992; MS210.004.017.00010 (Box 17)
    - Maps, 1992; MS210.004.017.00013 (Box 17)
    - Maps, MS210.004.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Other sites, 1905 -- 2002; MS210.004.029
    - Africa A-C, 1994; MS210.004.017.00015 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1994; MS210.004.017.00016 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1986; MS210.004.017.00017 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1986; MS210.004.017.00018 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1994; MS210.004.017.00019 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1994; MS210.004.017.00020 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1997; MS210.004.017.00021 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1982; MS210.004.017.00022 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1986; MS210.004.017.00023 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1982; MS210.004.017.00024 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1992; MS210.004.017.00025 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1992; MS210.004.017.00026 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1992; MS210.004.017.00027 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1992; MS210.004.017.00028 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1992 -- 1994; MS210.004.017.00029 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1994; MS210.004.017.00030 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1997; MS210.004.017.00031 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1997; MS210.004.017.00032 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1997; MS210.004.017.00033 (Box 17)
    - Africa A-C, 1997; MS210.004.017.00034 (Box 17)
    - Africa D-L, 1980; MS210.004.018.00001 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1986; MS210.004.018.00002 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1986; MS210.004.018.00003 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1990; MS210.004.018.00004 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1983 -- 1990; MS210.004.018.00005 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1990 -- 1998; MS210.004.018.00006 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1980; MS210.004.018.00007 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1990; MS210.004.018.00008 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1992; MS210.004.018.00009 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1989; MS210.004.018.00010 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1989; MS210.004.018.00011 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1989; MS210.004.018.00012 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1989; MS210.004.018.00013 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1989; MS210.004.018.00014 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1989 -- 1990; MS210.004.018.00015 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1990; MS210.004.018.00016 (Box 18)
    - Africa D-L, 1979 -- 1980; MS210.004.018.00017 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1994; MS210.004.018.00018 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1994; MS210.004.018.00019 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1994; MS210.004.018.00020 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1998; MS210.004.018.00021 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1998; MS210.004.018.00022 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1986; MS210.004.018.00023 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1980 -- 1989; MS210.004.018.00024 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1989; MS210.004.018.00025 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1994; MS210.004.018.00026 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1994 -- 1998; MS210.004.018.00027 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1980 -- 1989; MS210.004.018.00028 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1986; MS210.004.018.00029 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1986; MS210.004.018.00030 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1986; MS210.004.018.00031 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, MS210.004.018.00032 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, MS210.004.018.00033 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1980 -- 1983; MS210.004.018.00034 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1981; MS210.004.018.00035 (Box 18)
    - Africa M-Z, 1980 -- 1991; MS210.004.019.00001 (Box 19)
    - Africa M-Z, 1986 -- 1998; MS210.004.019.00002 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00003 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00004 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00005 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00006 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00007 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00008 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00009 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, 1988; MS210.004.019.00010 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, MS210.004.019.00011 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, MS210.004.019.00012 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, MS210.004.019.00013 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, MS210.004.019.00014 (Box 19)
    - Ankara and Istanbul, MS210.004.019.00015 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, MS210.004.019.00016 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, MS210.004.019.00017 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, MS210.004.019.00018 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, MS210.004.019.00019 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, 1974; MS210.004.019.00020 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, MS210.004.019.00021 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, MS210.004.019.00022 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, 1989; MS210.004.019.00023 (Box 19)
    - Army: Sites and People, 1989; MS210.004.019.00024 (Box 19)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.019.00025 (Box 19)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.019.00026 (Box 19)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.019.00027 (Box 19)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.019.00028 (Box 19)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.019.00029 (Box 19)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.019.00030 (Box 19)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.020.00001 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.020.00002 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.020.00003 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.020.00004 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.020.00005 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1979; MS210.004.020.00006 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1993; MS210.004.020.00007 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1993; MS210.004.020.00008 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1993; MS210.004.020.00009 (Box 20)
    - Britain, the North, 1993; MS210.004.020.00010 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Byrsa, 2000; MS210.004.020.00011 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Other Sites, MS210.004.020.00012 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Other Sites, 1983 -- 1985; MS210.004.020.00013 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Other Sites, 1986; MS210.004.020.00014 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Other Sites, 1983 -- 1995; MS210.004.020.00015 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Other Sites, 1905 -- 1992; MS210.004.020.00016 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Other Sites, 1998; MS210.004.020.00017 (Box 20)
    - Carthage Other Sites, 1980 -- 1998; MS210.004.020.00018 (Box 20)
    - Chichen-Itza, 2001; MS210.004.020.00019 (Box 20)
    - Chichen-Itza, 2001; MS210.004.020.00020 (Box 20)
    - Cosa, 2002; MS210.004.020.00021 (Box 20)
    - Cosa, 2002; MS210.004.020.00022 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00023 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00024 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00025 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00026 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00027 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00028 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00029 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00030 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00031 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00032 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00033 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00034 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00035 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00036 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00037 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00038 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00039 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.020.00040 (Box 20)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00002 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00004 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00007 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00008 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00010 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00011 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00012 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00013 (Box 21)
    - Euphrates, 1988; MS210.004.021.00014 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1990; MS210.004.021.00015 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1990; MS210.004.021.00016 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1981; MS210.004.021.00017 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1974; MS210.004.021.00018 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1974; MS210.004.021.00019 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, MS210.004.021.00020 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1977; MS210.004.021.00021 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1976 -- 1994; MS210.004.021.00022 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1974; MS210.004.021.00023 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1981; MS210.004.021.00024 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1981; MS210.004.021.00025 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1994; MS210.004.021.00026 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1974 -- 1981; MS210.004.021.00027 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1989; MS210.004.021.00028 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, MS210.004.021.00029 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, MS210.004.021.00030 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1974; MS210.004.021.00031 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1974; MS210.004.021.00032 (Box 21)
    - Germany, MS210.004.021.00033 (Box 21)
    - Germany, MS210.004.021.00034 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1974; MS210.004.021.00035 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1974; MS210.004.021.00036 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1983; MS210.004.021.00037 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1983; MS210.004.021.00038 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1983; MS210.004.021.00039 (Box 21)
    - Germany, MS210.004.021.00040 (Box 21)
    - Gaul, 1993; MS210.004.021.00041 (Box 21)
    - Germany, 1987; MS210.004.022.00001 (Box 22)
    - Germany, 1987; MS210.004.022.00002 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00003 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00004 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00005 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00006 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00007 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00008 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00009 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00010 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00011 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00012 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00013 (Box 22)
    - Germany: Limes 1995, MS210.004.022.00014 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1974; MS210.004.022.00015 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1974; MS210.004.022.00016 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1967; MS210.004.022.00017 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1967 -- 1993; MS210.004.022.00018 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1967; MS210.004.022.00019 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1967; MS210.004.022.00020 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1974; MS210.004.022.00021 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1974; MS210.004.022.00022 (Box 22)
    - Greece, MS210.004.022.00023 (Box 22)
    - Greece, 1988; MS210.004.022.00024 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1976; MS210.004.022.00025 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1976; MS210.004.022.00026 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00027 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00028 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00029 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00030 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00031 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00032 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00033 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00034 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00035 (Box 22)
    - Hungary and Romania, 1997; MS210.004.022.00036 (Box 22)
    - Aqua Claudia, 2002; MS210.004.023.00001 (Box 23)
    - Isola Sacra, 2002; MS210.004.023.00002 (Box 23)
    - Isola Sacra, 2002; MS210.004.023.00003 (Box 23)
    - Israel, MS210.004.023.00004 (Box 23)
    - Israel, MS210.004.023.00005 (Box 23)
    - Israel, 1967; MS210.004.023.00006 (Box 23)
    - Israel, MS210.004.023.00007 (Box 23)
    - Israel, 1967; MS210.004.023.00008 (Box 23)
    - Israel, MS210.004.023.00009 (Box 23)
    - Israel, 1967; MS210.004.023.00010 (Box 23)
    - Israel, MS210.004.023.00011 (Box 23)
    - Israel, MS210.004.023.00012 (Box 23)
    - Ostia, 2002; MS210.004.023.00013 (Box 23)
    - Ostia, 2002; MS210.004.023.00014 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1967; MS210.004.023.00015 (Box 23)
    - Rome, MS210.004.023.00016 (Box 23)
    - Rome, MS210.004.023.00017 (Box 23)
    - Rome, MS210.004.023.00018 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1993; MS210.004.023.00019 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1993; MS210.004.023.00020 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1993; MS210.004.023.00021 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1993; MS210.004.023.00022 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1993 -- 1994; MS210.004.023.00023 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1994; MS210.004.023.00024 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1994; MS210.004.023.00025 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1994; MS210.004.023.00026 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1994; MS210.004.023.00027 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1994; MS210.004.023.00028 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 2002; MS210.004.023.00029 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1987; MS210.004.023.00030 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1987; MS210.004.023.00031 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1987; MS210.004.023.00032 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1987; MS210.004.023.00033 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1987; MS210.004.023.00034 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1987; MS210.004.023.00035 (Box 23)
    - Rome, 1987; MS210.004.024.00001 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1988; MS210.004.024.00002 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1988; MS210.004.024.00003 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00004 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00005 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00006 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00007 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00008 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00009 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00010 (Box 24)
    - Rome, 1989; MS210.004.024.00011 (Box 24)
    - RCRF Ephesus, 2000; MS210.004.024.00012 (Box 24)
    - Sette Fnestre, 2002; MS210.004.024.00013 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1975; MS210.004.024.00014 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1975; MS210.004.024.00015 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, MS210.004.024.00016 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1989; MS210.004.024.00017 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1989; MS210.004.024.00018 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1977; MS210.004.024.00019 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1975; MS210.004.024.00020 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1989; MS210.004.024.00021 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1989; MS210.004.024.00022 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, MS210.004.024.00023 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1989; MS210.004.024.00024 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1975 -- 1989; MS210.004.024.00025 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, MS210.004.024.00026 (Box 24)
    - Southern England, 1975; MS210.004.024.00027 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, 1974; MS210.004.024.00028 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, 1981; MS210.004.024.00029 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, 1981; MS210.004.024.00030 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, MS210.004.024.00031 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, MS210.004.024.00032 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, MS210.004.024.00033 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.024.00034 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.024.00035 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.024.00036 (Box 24)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.025.00001 (Box 25)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.025.00002 (Box 25)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.025.00003 (Box 25)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.025.00004 (Box 25)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.025.00005 (Box 25)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.025.00006 (Box 25)
    - Spain and Italy, 1993; MS210.004.025.00007 (Box 25)
    - St Romain-en-Gal, 2000; MS210.004.025.00008 (Box 25)
    - Tulum, 2001; MS210.004.025.00009 (Box 25)
    - Tulum, 2001; MS210.004.025.00010 (Box 25)
    - Vienne, 2000; MS210.004.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Carthage Slide show, 1979 -- 2002; MS210.004.030
    - Carthage 1 Left, 1979 -- 2002; MS210.004.025.00012 (Box 25)
    - Carthage 1 Left, 1982 -- 2000; MS210.004.025.00013 (Box 25)
    - Carthage 1 Left, 1981 -- 1986; MS210.004.025.00014 (Box 25)
    - Carthage 2 Right, 1982 -- 2002; MS210.004.025.00015 (Box 25)
    - Carthage 2 Right, 1979; MS210.004.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Carthage, 1994; MS210.004.034.00001 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Carthage -interny x prints, enlargement for exhibits, MS210.004.034.00002 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Photographs of Cartahge site, MS210.004.034.00003 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - P2, MS210.004.034.00004 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Photographs of Carthage sites, MS210.004.034.00005 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - R2 - Carthage, MS210.004.034.00006 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Photographs of students and Carthage site for exhibits, MS210.004.034.00007 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Exhibit Text, MS210.004.034.00008 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
- Carthage Site Maps, 1913 -- 1998; 1978 -- 1998; MS210.005; 7.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains maps detailing the UNESCO's Second Canadian Archaeological dig at the 2CC Northern Sector of the Theodosian wall and the archaeological dig sponsored by Trinity University at the Hill of Odeon. There are published versions of the archaeological maps and hand-drawn stratigraphic maps.
  This series is arranged in two sub-series.
  - Published Maps, 1913 -- 1998; 1978 -- 1998; MS210.005.001; 7.75 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains printed and published maps from between 1913 and 1998, UNESCO's Second Canadian Archaeological dig at the 2CC Northern Sector of the Theodosian wall and the archaeological dig sponsored by Trinity University at the Hill of Odeon. The maps show the evolution of the dig locations as trenches were further uncovered and evaluated. There are also maps of Carthage and Tunisia.
    - Ruines de Carthage Part 1, 1913; MS210.005.001.00001 (Box 1)
      Maps (documents)
    - Ruines de Carthage Part 2, 1913; MS210.005.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Ruines de Carthage Part 3, 1913; MS210.005.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Environs de Tunis, 1953; MS210.005.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Carthage Map "44-45", 1958; MS210.005.001.00005 (Box data_value_missing_89dee03018a7302e2b9eb234f7288880)
    - Canada Carthage Site CC-2 Cadrillage Theorique des Rues Romaines (Audette), 1976; MS210.005.001.00006 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Canada Carthage Site CC-2 Plans des Operations (Audette), 1976; MS210.005.001.00007 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Canada Carthage Implantation des Sites, Releve des Rues Romaines, 1976; MS210.005.001.00008 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Main Site, 1976 -- 1978; MS210.005.001.00009 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Topography map (Alain and Andre Audette), 1976 -- 1978; MS210.005.001.00010 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Topography map, 1976 -- 1978; MS210.005.001.00011 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Spare set of plans, MS210.005.001.00012 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations, Main Site, excavations (Audette) Figure 3, 1976 -- 1978; MS210.005.001.00013 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations, Main Site, excavations (Audette) Figure 3, 1976 -- 1978; MS210.005.001.00014 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Main Site (Erdmer), 1976 -- 1979; MS210.005.001.00015 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site, 1976 -- 1979; MS210.005.001.00016 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site, 1976 -- 1979; MS210.005.001.00017 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site, 1976 -- 1979; MS210.005.001.00018 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site, 1976 -- 1979; MS210.005.001.00019 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site, 1976 -- 1979; MS210.005.001.00020 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Section, Trenches 4B-4C, 1978; MS210.005.001.00021 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Section, Trenches 4B-4C, 1978; MS210.005.001.00022 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations, Trench 7 Theodosian Wall and Tower, 1978 -- 1979; MS210.005.001.00023 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Field Survey and Street Grid, 1979; MS210.005.001.00024 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Field Survey and Street Grid, 1979; MS210.005.001.00025 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Main Site (Audette 76, 78; Erdmer 79, 80), 1976 -- 1980; MS210.005.001.00026 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site, 1976 -- 1980; MS210.005.001.00027 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site, 1976 -- 1980; MS210.005.001.00028 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Main Site and Street Grid map on Display Board, 1976 -- 1980; MS210.005.001.00029 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavation with street grid, 1980 season, MS210.005.001.00030 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Map, 1982; MS210.005.001.00031 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Poster Map, 1985; MS210.005.001.00032 (Box data_value_missing_87fbd8863af5c57c69c63481083f09a9)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavation - Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00033 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavation - Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State Blue Print Negatives, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00034 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavation - Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00035 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)